Some extra-terrestrials aren't friendly.
Xtro is a science fiction, horror film directed by Harry Bromley Davenport.
Tony's father Sam, abducted by aliens three years earlier, returns to earth and seeks out his
wife and son, but Rachel has since been living with Joe and the reunion is awkward.
Joe doesn't trust Sam, and Rachel can't quite decide
what her feelings are for her two men.
Sam is not the same as when he left, and he begins
affecting Tony in frightening ways.
Sam Philips, played by Philip Sayer.
Rachel Philips, played by Bernice Stegers.
Joe Daniels, played by Danny Brainin.
Analise Mercier, played by Maryam D'Abo.
Tony Phillips, played by Simon Nash.
Clown, played by Peter Mandell.
Xtro is a 1983 British science fiction horror film written
and directed by Harry Bromley Davenport.
The film stars Bernice Stegers, Philip Sayer, Simon Nash, and Maryam d'Abo.
The film focuses on a man who was abducted by aliens and
returns back to his wife and son three years later.
The film received largely negative reviews from critics,
while the special effects were praised.
The film explores themes of rape, kidnapping, pregnancy, transformation, clown.
The tone is dark and thought_provoking and mind_bending.